All of us are human. None of us are immune.
A Cure for Wellness is a horror, mystery, science
fiction film directed by Gore Verbinski.
An ambitious young executive is sent to retrieve his company's CEO from an idyllic but mysterious "wellness center" at a
remote location in the Swiss Alps but soon suspects that the spa's miraculous treatments are not what they seem.
Lockhart, played by Dane DeHaan.
Volmer, played by Jason Isaacs.
Hannah, played by Mia Goth.
Pembroke, played by Harry Groener.
Victoria Watkins, played by Celia Imrie.
Deputy Director, played by Adrian Schiller.
A Cure for Wellness is a 2017 psychological horror film directed
by Gore Verbinski and written by Justin Haythe.
Haythe and Verbinski were inspired by Thomas Mann's 1924 novel The
Magic Mountain while coming up with the idea for the film.
Starring Dane DeHaan, Jason Isaacs, and Mia Goth, the plot follows a young executive who is sent to
retrieve his company's CEO from a mysterious rehabilitation center in the Swiss Alps.
An international co-production based in the United States, Germany, and Luxembourg, the film was shot on
location at various German locations, including Hohenzollern Castle in Baden-Württemberg.
A Cure for Wellness was released on February 17, 2017, by 20th Century Fox and received generally mixed reviews from critics, who
praised its visuals, cinematography, performances and ambition, but criticized its length, script and narrative.
It grossed $26 million against its $40 million
production budget, making it a box-office bomb.
The film explores themes of darkness, therapist,
switzerland, mountain, wellness.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and mind_bending.